Can I see the comics?
만화 좀 보자
This is the New York Times.
이건 뉴욕 타임즈야
만화 좀 봐도 돼요?
Okay, may I see the comics?
I thought you were
taking Ross to the game.
오빠 데리고
경기장 간다고 했잖아?
여기서 만나기로 했어
-We are. He's meeting us here.
-No, Rachel's meeting us here!
안돼! 우리도 여기서
레이첼을 만나
살다보면 만날 수도 있지
Come on!
They can be in the same room.
어젯밤에 일 날 뻔했어
-You should've been there last night.
-What happened?
무슨 일인데?
Ross was hanging out at our place.
로스가 우리 집에
놀러와 있는데
Rachel comes over to borrow
some moisturizer from Chandler
레이첼이 챈들러 영양크림을
빌리러 왔다가...
야, 잠깐!
자세히 말할 필요가 있어?
레이첼이 뭔가를 빌리러 왔다
How hard is it to say "something"?
Rachel came over to borrow "something."
Anyway, her and Ross just started
yelling at each other.
어쨌든 둘이 서로에게
소리 치고 난리였어
Why was he yelling at her?
He slept with someone else.
로스가 왜 소리를 질러?
문제의 원인은 자기면서
잠깐 떨어져 있던 사이에
발생한 일이니까
He says they were on a break
when it happened...
...so she should've
forgiven him by now.
지금쯤은 용서하라는 거지
정말 뻔뻔하네!
He is so unreasonable! God!
물론 말뜻은 이해를 해
Although I understand what he means.
이거 '추적 60분' 같다
Oh, my God!
This is like 60 Minutes...
사람들이 제약 회사에
항의를 하면
...when at first you're mad that
pharmaceutical company made the drug.
And then, you just feel bad
for the people, because...
발모제를 만들라고 해서
만들었는데 뭔 소리냐는 거!
...they needed
to make their hair grow.
내 기분 알아?
부모님 이혼 때랑 똑같애
You know, this is like
when my parents got divorced.
I hope Ross doesn't try to kidnap me
after Cub Scouts.
둘이, 날 두고 싸우지
말아야 할텐데
꿈을 꿨는데, 로스랑
레이첼 사이가 좋았어
I dreamed that Ross and Rachel
were still together.
And we were all
hanging out and happy.
우리 모두 모여서
행복한 얼굴이었지
나도 그런 꿈 꿨어
I had the same dream.
내 꿈엔, 복사가게
아가씨가 안 나와
-And nobody slept with the xerox girl.
-Oh, I had the opposite dream.
내 꿈엔 또렷하게 나와
Maybe it's gonna be okay.
I mean, it's been a week.
괜찮을 거야
일주일이나 됐잖아
난 누구와 싸우면
일주일을 못 넘겨
It never takes me more than a week
to get over a relationship.
It never takes you more than a shower
일주일 이상 만나야
싸우기도 하지
왔구나? 가자!
어서 가서 쇼를 봐야지!
Let's go! Let's hit the road.
Let's get the show on it.
커피 한 잔만 하자
Let me get coffee.
커피 맛 괜찮은 집이
이 근처에 있어
I know the best coffeehouse.
And it's close.
여기선 안 판대?
Closer than here?
Oh, look! I found coffee!
여기 커피가 있네!
Okay, let's skedaddle.
빨리 마셔
다른 사람이
마시던 건 안 마셔
I'm not gonna drink
somebody's old coffee.
네, 공주마마
Okay, Your Highness.
"Rachel, I'm really sorry."
"Okay, Ross. Wanna get back together?"
"레이첼, 미안해"
"괜찮아, 로스
우리 다시 합칠까?"
"그래, 좋아"
"Yeah, okay."
이런 말 안 들리니?
Did anyone else hear that?
The One Without the Ski Trip
- 로스 있어?
- 아니
Is he here?
Here's your moisturizer.
영양크림 잘 썼어
- 안녕
신나는 일이 있어
들어봐
You guys are gonna love me!
Okay, check it out.
Thursday night, five tickets.
목요일 밤, 티켓 5장
캘빈 클라인 란제리 쇼
Calvin Klein lingerie show,
and you guys are coming with me.
우리 같이 가자
내 말 못 들었니?
I said that out loud, right?
들었어, 그런데 그 날은...
Yes, it's just that
we kind of already...
로스랑 계획이 있어
... made plans with Ross.
그래, 알았어
Well, okay.
Well, there you go.
잘 됐네
로스가 가정용 영화스크린을
샀다고, 같이 보자고 했어
It's just, he got this new
home-theater dealy...
...and he wants us to check it out.
He's excited about it too.
로스가 되게 신났어
영화 시간표까지 준비했더라구
He even recorded showtimes
on his answering machine.
- 정말 미안해
- 괜찮아
-We're sorry, honey.
-Oh, it's okay.
Rach, it's not that
we don't want to. Really.
레이첼!
싫어서 거절한 게 아냐
Are we talking models
in their underwear?
모델이 속옷만 입고 나와?
And heels.
하이힐도 신지
Ross did ask us first,
and we set that night aside.
로스가 선약이라
깰 수가 없어
아냐, 선약을 지켜야
공정한 거지
Come on. If he asked you first,
it's only fair.
Oh, boy, do I feel bad!
- 정말 기분 이상해
- 그래
정말 그래
Very bad.
- 챈들러, 뭐 하는 거야?
- 챈들러?
Chandler, what are you doing?
이게 뭐지!
Oh, my God!
You're smoking again?
다시 피우는 거야?
어제 피우기 시작해서
아직도 피운다
Well, actually,
yesterday, I was smoking again.
Today I'm smoking, still.
Why would you start again
after chewing all that quitting gum?
금연껌 열심히 씹어서
끊더니 다시 피워?
This is just like
my parents' divorce...
부모님 이혼할 때랑 기분이
비슷하다고 했잖아
그 무렵에 담배를 배웠거든
...which is when
I first started smoking.
Weren't you 9?
9살 때?
응
I'm telling you something,
that first smoke after naptime....
쭈쭈바를 먹고 나서
첫 담배를 피웠지
That's great.
With my luck, that's him.
좋아! 드디어 왔다
Him? Ross?
- 누구? 로스?
- 아니
찬송가 253장
'주님은 나의 목자시니'
No, "Hymn" 253:
"His Eyes Are on the Sparrow."
When my parents got divorced, I started
using humor as a defense mechanism.
부모님이 이혼하고 나서
방어 수단으로 농담을 익혔지
Hi. Do you guys have weekend plans?
나야!
이번 주말에 계획 있니?
언니랑 통화했는데
Because my sister says we can spend
the weekend at her cabin, skiing.
주말에 별장을 빌려줄테니
거기서 스키 타래
I'm asking you first, right?
I'm playing by the rules.
내가 먼저 물었지?
선약 우선의 원칙!
- 물론이지
- 좋아
Absolutely.
Chandler! You're smoking?
What are you doing?
챈들러! 담배 피워?
왜 그래?
닥쳐요! 당신은 새엄마예요
Shut up!
You're not my real mom!
Could you close that window?
My nipples could cut glass!
창문 좀 닫을래?
젖꼭지가 땡땡 얼었어
그래?
내 건 뚫고 나오려고 해
Really? Because mine
get me out of tickets.
너희들, 나와 함께 시간을
보내줘서 고마울 뿐이야
Look, I just wanna say I really
appreciate you spending time with me.
It's been a hard time right now,
so I just want to say thanks.
요즘 좀 힘들었는데
너희들 정말 고맙다
누가 쟤 좀 안아 줘라
난 창가에 있어야 돼
Somebody else hug him.
I have to stay by the window.
잠깐, 얘들아
How about this weekend, we have
a laser-disc marathon, okay?
이번 주말에 레이저디스크로
밤새 영화 보자
And maybe a tournament
on my new...
게임도 하는 거야
다트 판도 새로 샀다구
어때? 밤새 노는 거야!
...dart board! What do you think?
Two days of darts! It'll be great!
왕 신나지?
It'll be great for next weekend.
다음 주가 좋을 것 같은데
This weekend, guys.
아냐, 이번 주에 해
다음 주가 좋겠어
It'll be great for next weekend.
I mean, "lt'll be great."
그래야 왕 신나지
왜들 그래?
What's going on?
스키 타러 가기로 했거든
레이첼 언니네 별장에 가
We're sort of invited to go skiing.
You know, Rachel's sister's cabin?
So, for the whole weekend?
주말 내내?
미안하게 됐지만...
그게 선약이라서
We're really sorry,
but she did ask us first.
That's okay. If you
all have to go away...
그래, 괜찮아
너희들 모두 간다면
나 혼자 주말을 보낼게
...for the first weekend I'm
alone by myself...
난 모두 이해해
...then I totally understand.
I can stay. I'm gonna stay.
내가 남을게, 안 가도 돼
The last time I went,
I was afraid to leave the chair lift.
전에 스키장에 갔을 때
리프트에서 내리기 무서워서
계속 맴맴 돌았어
I just went round and round.
할머니 택시를 빌렸으니까
네가 운전해야지
We need you to drive us there
in your grandmother's cab.
내가 남을게
-But you know what? I'll stay.
-No, I'll stay. He's my brother.
아냐, 내가 남을게
우리 오빠잖아
- 날 동정하는 거야?
- 아냐!
What, a "pity stay"?
We're gonna have fun!
재밌게 놀자
맛있는 것도 해줄게
We can make fudge.
동정이 담긴 음식!
Pity food?
You know what?
I don't need any of you to stay.
됐어, 괜찮아, 나 때문에
남을 필요 없어, 다 가버려
Nobody stays.
Well, then, I might as well
offer to stay.
그럼 예의상 나도 남을게
로스가 맘에 걸리지 않니?
Does anybody else feel bad about Ross?
You think he's still mad?
오빠가 화났을까봐?
He's probably more mad since
you called him to borrow his goggles.
조이가 스키고글 빌려달라고
해서 더 화났을 거야
What? Mine aren't tinted.
로스 고글이 새 거야
챈들러!
왜?
What?
What does the sign say?
여기 글 안 보여?
'주여, 빛을 주소서'
"Beam me up, Jesus."
아니, '금연'이잖아
우리 할머니 차에선 금연이야
The "No Smoking" sign.
There's no smoking
in my grandmother's cab.
Well, then, I have to go
to the bathroom.
- 알았어... 화장실에서 피울게
- 제발...
Oh, please!
계획대로 주유소에서
세우면, 그때 가
No unscheduled stops.
You can go when we stop for gas.
There's a rest stop right up there.
Come on, I really have to go!
화장실 표지가 보여
진짜 화장실이 급해
Oh, now I have to go!
나도 가야돼
다 왔다
Here we go.
- 몸조심해
- 뭐?
-Brace yourself!
-What?
이제 알았어
-Aren't you gonna go?
-No, thanks.
- 넌 안 가니?
- 응, 됐어
Rachel never pees in public restrooms.
레이첼은 공중화장실 안 가
They never have any paper in there.
이런 덴 화장지가 없잖아
'화장지 없는 곳에
깔끔함 없다'
So my rule is, "No tissue, no tushy."
Well, if everybody's going....
모두가 간다면...
Don't close it!
The keys are in there!
닫으면 안돼!
차 키가 안에 있어!
안돼, 안돼!
-What's going on?
-My lighter's in there!
왜 그래?
라이터가 안에 있어
젠장!
Damn! The tailpipe's
not hot enough to light this.
배기관 열로는
불이 안 붙어
걱정 마, 열 수 있어
누구 옷걸이 없니?
I can open this.
Anybody got a coat hanger?
Oh, I do.
있어, 미안!
No, I took it out of my shirt
when I put it on this morning.
아침에 옷 꺼내 입으면서
장롱에 두고 왔다
부모님이 이혼하시고 나서
익힌 농담이 그런 식이야?
So if your parents hadn't divorced...
...you'd be able to answer a question
like a normal person?
Look, I just need a wire something
to jimmy it.
그냥 철사 줄 하나면 돼
그래! 너희들 브래지어에
철사 있잖아
One of you give me
your bra underwire.
- 뭐?
- 누구 가슴이 제일 크지?
- 뭐야?
Come on!
Who has the biggest boobs?
큰 가슴이 큰 브라를 할거고
거기엔 큰 철사가 있지
Whoever has the biggest boobs,
has the biggest bra and wire.
- 내 건 절대 안돼
- 내 것도 비싼 거야
-No!
-It's too expensive!
차에 타려면 철사가 필요해
맘대로 해
To get back in the car,
we need that wire.
Your call.
모니카가 제일 커
Monica's are the biggest.
These tiny little non-breasts?
Please! It's gotta be Rachel.
난 납작 가슴이야
레이첼이 크지
아냐, 눈속임이야
No, mine are deceptively small.
그게... 꼭 끼게 입거든
I mean, I actually sometimes
stuff my bra.
어쨌든 크긴 하겠지
Well, then, your bra would
still be big.
No, I stuff outside the bra.
내 거는 가슴이
다 나오도록 작아
숙녀분들, 빨리 합시다
Ladies, let's just compromise, okay?
Phoebe, Rachel,
take off Monica's bra.
피비, 레이첼!
모니카 브라 벗겨
- 됐어, 내 걸로 줄게
- 고마워
All right, forget it, never mind.
-You can have mine.
-Thank you.
그게 무슨 짓이야?
쓰레기통이 저기 있잖아
What are you doing?
There's a trash can right there.
내 흔적을 남겨 놔야
인디언이 와서 구해주지
I thought if I littered, that crying
lndian might come by and save us.
됐어, 받아
There.
Thank you, Phoebe.
That's very, very generous.
고마워, 피비
넌 정말... 착해
이젠 누구 엉덩이가
제일 큰가 보자
Now, let's decide
who has the nicest ass.
됐어!
And there you go!
챈들러!
창문 여는 걸
고맙게 생각해
Well, at least let me smoke it
to the good part!
좋아
이런!
왜?
-What's going on?
-What?
- 뭔데?
- 무슨 일인데?
전에도 이랬었어
Yeah, this has happened before.
-So you know how to fix it?
-Yep. Put more gas in.
고칠 수 있지?
응, 기름만 넣으면 돼
Hi. What are you doing here?
- 어서 와, 웬일이야?
- 안녕
그냥 궁금해서...
테입 받았지?
I was wondering,
when you and I split up...
...did you get the tape that was
half the last episode of M.A. S.H...
반은 드라마고 나머지는
인질이 구출되는 거
...and half the hostages coming home?
응, 지금 인질이
구출되는 거 보고 있어
But now it's Susan and me in Mexico
and the hostages coming home.
Where's Ben?
- 벤은 뭐해?
- 자고 있어
He's sleeping.
Is this a bad time?
내가 잘못 온 건가?
글쎄, 수잔이 곧 올 거야
기념일 축하하려구
Yeah, actually.
Susan's gonna be here any minute.
It's kind of an anniversary.
I thought you guys
got married in January.
결혼 기념일은 1월이잖아
A different kind of anniversary.
다른 기념일이야
어쨌든...
So anyway
Candles, champagne....
촛불, 샴페인...
기념일 좋지
Yeah, anniversaries are great...
... because love lasts forever,
you know?
사랑은 영원하리!
There's nothing like it
in this life. Money in the bank.
인생에서 소중한 건
은행에 돈만 있으면...
레이첼과 헤어졌어
So Rachel and I broke up.
- 로스, 안 됐다
- 그래
God, Ross, I am so sorry!
너랑 많은 얘기를 하고 싶지만
오늘은 할 일이 있으니까
You know what?
I wanna talk about this so much...
... but when we can really get into it.
내일 저녁식사나 할까?
-You free for dinner tomorrow?
-I'd love that.
- 그래, 좋아
- 그래, 그러자
Me too.
I guess it all started
when Rachel got this new job.
레이첼이 새 직장을
나가면서 시작됐어
좋아요
우리 데리러 온대
Triple A can pick us up.
- 됐어!
- 잘 됐다
What town are we near?
여기가 어디쯤이니?
Freemont.
프리, 프리몬트
웨스트몬트, 웨스트버그?
Westmont.
Westberg?
Why are you answering?
헷갈리게 하지마
Do you know
what route we're on?
도로 이름은 알지?
- 27번 국도일 거야
- 알았어
We are definitely on Route 27.
27번 국도,
공중화장실이에요
We are at a rest stop on Route 27
국도에 27번은 없대
There is no Route 27.
-Either 93 or 76.
-I don't know.
- 93번, 76번?
- 몰라, 미안해
I always slept in the back
when we drove here.
여기 올 때마다 항상 잤거든
76번 쪽으로 사람을 보내서
공중화장실마다 확인해주세요
Can you just send someone up and down
76 and check every rest stop?
아니면 93번 쪽으로요
And also 93?
알았어요
No, they don't do that.
그렇게는 못 한대
지나가는 차를 얻어 타자
Somebody will come and save us.
Who? Have you seen a car
in the last hour and a half?
뭐? 1시간 반 동안
차 한 대도 안 지나갔어
오빠한테 전화해
꼭 와줄 거야
We should call Ross.
Maybe he can get a car to get us.
안돼! 로스 차에는
절대 안 타
I am not getting in a car with Ross!
We will just have to...
차라리 여기서 살고 말지
...Iive here!
- 추워 죽겠어
- 싫어
-But it's so cold.
-No!
같은 차에 타고 싶지 않아
다른 방법을 생각해보자
I won't get in a car with him.
Think of something else.
조이와 챈들러가 온다
Joey and Chandler are back!
So the "going for help" went well?
어떻게 됐어?
여기 애연가 씨가
중간에서 쓰러지셨다
Smokey Joe here got halfway
to the highway and collapsed.
폐 용량이 벌써 찼나봐
I have the lung capacity
of a 2-year-old.
그런데 또 피워?
Then why are you smoking?
It's very unsettling.
불안할 땐 피워야 돼
Right? I mean,
it's pretty unbelievable.
그렇지?
정말 믿을 수가 없어
다들 떠났어
뒤도 안 돌아보더라
They just took off,
without even looking back.
나도 걔네들 필요 없어
I don't need them.
I've got you guys now as friends.
나도 너희들이 있잖아
너와 수잔
You and Susan.
수잔도 좋아할 거야
Susan will be so pleased.
Seven-one-seven?
717?
717이 어디야?
Where's 717?
You have more of these
for Susan, right?
수잔 음식은 남아있지?
아니, 괜찮아
피클이나 주면 돼
No, but that's okay.
I'll just put out pickles
or something.
로스? 다행이다
-Ross, thank God!
-Pheebs?
피비?
목소리가 왜 그래?
Why are you whispering?
날파리를 삼켰어
I ate a bug.
Hey, Rach! The tampons here
are only a penny.
여기 생리대가 너무 싸
많이 사두자
Let's stock up.
We're out of gas and don't know where
we are so we can't get a tow truck.
기름은 떨어지고, 어딘지도 몰라서
견인차를 못 불러
- 그래서 도와달라고?
- 응, 부탁해
Now you want a favor?
Yes, please.
자동차가 멈췄다니 안 됐다
I'm sorry your
car broke down, Pheebs...
근데 난 지금 진정한 친구와
노느라 바빠
... but I'm too busy with some of
my real friends right now.
But please call to let me know
you got home safely.
잘 도착하면 전화나 해줘
피비, 잠깐만
Phoebe, hang on a second.
Take my car.
Get your friends.
- 내 차로 친구들 도와줘
- 싫어, 죽어도...
No, I won't pick them up.
그래도 갈 거 다 알아
넌 바보가 아니니까
We both know you'll do it,
because you're not a jerk.
여기서 30분간 투덜대다가
친구들을 구할래?
So you can sulk here for half an hour,
then go get them...
아니면, 나를 구해주고
차안에서 투덜댈래?
-...or save time and sulk in the car.
-Rachel doesn't
레이첼이 싫어할...
레이첼이 마크와 사랑에 빠져
널 찬 건 안 됐어
I'm sorry Rachel dumped you for Mark...
...and you're the innocent victim
in this.
일방적으로 당한 건 안 됐지만
그런 일로 친구를 버릴래?
But don't punish your friends
for what Rachel did.
Yeah, you're right.
네 말이 맞아
Phoebe, hang on.
Ross wants to say something.
피비, 로스가 할 말 있대
뭐?
What?
You slept with someone else?
너 딴 여자랑 잤어?
헤어지는 중에 그런 거야!
We were on a break!
어딘데?
내가 갈게
We were
Where are you? I'll find you.
You slept with another woman?
다른 여자랑 잠을 자?
너도 그랬잖아
Oh, you're one to talk.
Okay, done!
좋아, 됐어!
'움도'가 뭐야?
What's "pleh"?
'도움'이란 단어를 거꾸로 해서
헬기가 하늘에서 읽게 한 거야
That's "help" spelled backwards...
...so that the helicopters can read it
from the air.
What's "dufus" spelled backwards?
헬기 창문이 거울이야?
차다! 온다!
Car! Car!
우연히 로스가 왔네!
Oh, it's Ross on one of his drives!
어서 와!
What is he doing here?
어떻게 된 거니?
널 구하러 오셨다
He is saving your butt.
한 발을 안 내리는 이유는
누군가 싫다면 가려구
Unless I'm stepping on
some toes here...
...in which case
I could just mosey on.
I have plenty of people to help
on the interstate.
오는 길에, 다른 사람들에게
말도 해놨어
- 그러지 말고 내려, 고마워!
- 좋아, 잘 했다
-Come on!
-We need your help, please!
Fine! Fine!
안녕!
어차피 도움도 안돼
Oh, no! Now it's
not gonna make any sense.
You guys...
이제 로스를 어쩌지?
먼길을 와줬잖아
...what do we do about Ross?
He drove all the way up here.
그냥 돌려보내, 아니면
데리고 갈까?
Just send him back,
then we'll go skiing?
골치가 지끈거린다
This is horrible.
It's just horrible.
로스한테 같이 가자고 할까?
Should we ask Ross to come along?
레이첼은 어쩌고?
부탁을 해볼까?
But what about Rachel?
How are we gonna even ask her?
Ask me what?
뭘 부탁해?
오빠도 가면 안 돼?
If it might be okay if
Ross came skiing?
No, I wasn't gonna ask that.
난 안 물었다
You guys are unbelievable.
No, he cannot come!
너희들 정말 너무해
같이 가기 싫어
- 뭐라고?
- 머리 아프다구
-Excuse me?
-It's horrible!
그 잘난 별장에
나도 갈 수 있을까?
Oh, please? Can't I come
to your special, magical cabin?
Why would you even want to come?
You're a horrible skier.
거기 가서 뭘 하려구?
스키도 못 타잖아
가슴이 미어지네!
내 스키 솜씨를 욕해?
Hitting me where it hurts!
My ski skills!
Here we go again.
또 시작이군
I can't handle this, you guys.
- 어째야 할지 모르겠다
- 난 할 수 있어
I can handle it.
"Handle" is my middle name.
내 이름을 잘 보면...
'할 수 있다'라는 뜻이 있대
Actually, it's the middle part
of my first name.
됐어, 기름 다 채웠어
All right, Pheebs, your cab's ready.
좋아, 가자
Let's go.
안 고맙지?
You're welcome.
I'm sorry. Were you speaking to me,
or sleeping with someone else?
미안! 나한테 한 말이야,
아님 그녀에게 한 말이야?
헤어지는 중이었어!
We were on a break!
Why don't you just put that
on your answering machine?
매번 대답하지 말고
전화 인사말에 녹음해 둬
내 말엔 일리가 있어
나만 이러는 게 아냐
It's valid, and I'm not the only one
who thinks so.
모니카도 동의한다구
Monica agrees with me.
What?
뭐?
I don't know.
난 몰라
어젯밤에 그랬잖아
You said it last night.
난 이해한다고만 했어
What I said
was that I understood.
조이가 동의를 했지
Joey is the one who agreed with you.
그래
Really, Joey?
정말 그랬어?
What?
뭐?
You know what?
There is no right or wrong here.
얘들아, 옳고 그른 답은 없어
I think it's very obvious
who's wrong here.
아니, 분명하게 답이 있어
조이는 답을 알걸
Obviously not to Joey.
What?
뭐?
- 조이와 모니카도 동의하는데...
- 친구가 어떻게 알아...
-Joey and Monica feel the way I do!
-You and this innocent puppy act!
내가 지금 뭐하게?
Hey, guess who I am?
그만해! 얘들아!
Look what you're doing to Chandler!
챈들러 좀 봐!
Look. We know that this is
really, really hard for you guys.
너희들 지금 힘든 거 알아
너희 둘이 사랑하지
않아도 돼
You don't have to love each other.
You don't even have to like
each other much right now.
좋아하지 않아도 괜찮아
하지만, 제발 주변을
돌아볼 순 없니?
But please, find a way
to be around each other.
And not put us in the middle.
우리를 사이에 두고
이러지 마
최소한, 그냥 친구로서
함께 있을 순 없는 거야?
Otherwise, I mean, that's just it
for us hanging out together.
이런 모습이 좋아?
Is that what you want?
아니
이성적으로 생각해
Can you be civil?
그래
I can.
그럴게
좋아, 어서 차에 타
난 더 추워, 브라도 빼줬잖아
Good, let's get back in the car.
It's freezing...
...and my chest is unsupported.
잠깐, 기다려봐
Wait a second!
어떻게 하지?
누구랑 누가 가지?
I mean, what are we doing?
Who's going with who?
그냥 너희끼리 가라
Look, you guys should go.
괜찮아, 너희들 계획이고...
You know,
you planned this all out...
망치고 싶진 않아
어서들 가
...and I don't wanna ruin it.
So just go.
You drove all the way up here.
- 그래도 먼길을 왔는데...
- 정말이야
I've got to take
the car back anyway.
캐롤 차도 돌려주고
우리 아들이나 볼래
I'm spending all day
tomorrow with Ben.
It's fine, okay? Just go.
No guilt, I promise.
괜찮아, 어서 가
삐진 거 아냐
고마워
Thank you.
We'll call you when we get back.
- 돌아가서 전화할게
- 그래
Maybe we can, like,
go to a movie or something.
- 나중에 영화라도 보자
- 그래
텔레비전이라도 봐!
Or the rodeo!
- 그거 좋겠다
- 간다
That would be great.
나도 도로에 엎어질 만큼
힘들었어
I was being Shelley Winters
from The Poseidon Adventure.
I know.
알아
Bye!
갈게!
로스!
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
밤늦게 미안해
내가 깨웠어?
Were you sleeping?
- 아니!
- 다행이다
Oh, great.
배터리가 나가서 갈았어
비싼 걸로 했는데, 괜찮지?
I had to get you a new battery.
I got the best I could.
You don't want to skimp there.
아주 잘했어, 로스
You're a genius.
It came to about $112.
112달러 들었어, 제기랄!
새벽에 깨웠더니 비싸
But what the hell,
call it an even 110?
- 됐어, 내일 줄게
- 그래
I'll pay you tomorrow. Bye!
잘 가
So they all took off.
친구들이 떠나는 걸
지켜보자니 힘 빠지더라
It was pretty hard
watching them go, you know?
알았어, 잘 가
Yeah, okay.
Bye.
So I'm gonna take off then.
나도 떠나버릴 거야